

JOEDERICO AREVALO

Prk. CKK, Brgy. Guinhalaran **S**ilay City, 6116, PH



+639925114539

judithekuletz.ja@gmail.com

SKILLS

HTML **JQuery** Database Management Reliability React.JS PHP Network Management JavaScript Microsoft Excel/Words Laravel

LANGUAGE

English Tagalog Hiligaynon

REFERENCES

RAMIL D. BORROMEO 09155165513

DIDOY BERNAL 09209490951

FREYA BAYONA 09331818099

ABOUT ME

PHP WEB DEVELOPER

I am an expert on the ground of Web development and can do many things related to the job. I am quite adept in coding and markup languages and in creating some applications. I developed some systems in some company's and installed in their local servers.

I am self-taught, but I honestly believe that with the amount of tutorials on YouTube, and in the PHP community, one can learn everything-including HTML, CSS, PHP and JavaScript. Currently, I'm learning React. Js and Laravel. I've tried to make my living as a freelance Full Stack Web Developer.

WORK EXPERIENCE

- Back Office Dept. Head/POS & Server Admin. (Feb. 2017 - Present) LOPUE'S SAN SEBASTIAN CORP. **Bacolod City**
- Customer Service Representative (Feb. 2016 - Nov. 2016) **MUNSTERIFIC** Bacolod City
- IT Assistant (May 2015 - Nov. 2015) MERZCI **Bacolod City**

PERSONAL DETAILS

Date of Birth Nationality July 17, 1996 **FILIPINO**

Marital Status Age

Single 26 years old

EDUCATION

 Programming National Certification IV (PNC-IV) /Information Technology Programming (ITP)

STI-West Negros University Bacolod City (2014-2015)

High School Diploma

Doña Hortencia Salas Benedicto National High School La Carlota City (2012-2013)